Papers of the National War Labor Board on Microfilm 5752 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Executive Session Minutes coninued; Transcripts of Proceedings (Selected Cases) (Reel 13)
  - Transcripts of Proceedings, 1918; 15 (Reel 13)
    July 6, 1918. 46 pp.
- Transcripts of Proceedings (Selected Cases) continued (Reel 14)
  - Transcripts of Proceedings, 1918; 1 (Reel 14)
    July 17, 1918. 281 pp.
  - Transcripts of Proceedings, 1918; 2 (Reel 14)
    July 18, 1918. 202 pp.
  - Transcripts of Proceedings, 1918; 3 (Reel 14)
    August 15, 1918. 18 pp.
  - Transcripts of Proceedings, 1918; 4 (Reel 14)
    September 23, 1918. 7 pp.
  - Transcripts of Proceedings: Employees v. General Electric. Lynn, MA., 1918; 5 (Reel 14)
    August 5, 1918. 35 pp.
  - Transcripts of Proceedings, 1918; 6 (Reel 14)
    August 8, 1918. 3 pp.
  - Transcripts of Proceedings, 1918; 7 (Reel 14)
    August 9, 1918. 119 pp.
  - Transcripts of Proceedings, 1918; 8 (Reel 14)
    August 12, 1918. 165 pp.
  - Transcripts of Proceedings, 1918; 9 (Reel 14)
    August 12, 1918. 15 pp.
  - Transcripts of Proceedings, 1918; 10 (Reel 14)
    August 13, 1918. 159 pp.
- Transcripts of Proceedings (Selected Cases) continued (Reel 15)
  - Transcripts of Proceedings, 1918; 1 (Reel 15)
    August 14, 1918. 164 pp.
  - Transcripts of Proceedings, 1918; 2 (Reel 15)
    August 16, 1918. 159 pp.
  - Transcripts of Proceedings, 1918; 3 (Reel 15)
    August 19, 1918. 133 pp.
  - Transcripts of Proceedings, 1918; 4 (Reel 15)
    August 21, 1918. 68 pp.
  - Transcripts of Proceedings, 1918; 5 (Reel 15)
    August 22, 1918. 121 pp.
  - Transcripts of Proceedings, 1918; 6 (Reel 15)
    August 23, 1918. 98 pp.
  - Transcripts of Proceedings, 1918; 7 (Reel 15)
    August 26, 1918. 142 pp.
  - Transcripts of Proceedings, 1918; 8 (Reel 15)
    August 27, 1918. 77 pp.
  - Transcripts of Proceedings, 1918; 9 (Reel 15)
    September 24, 1918. 99 pp.
- Case Files (Selected Cases) (Reel 16)
  - Commercial Telegraphers et al. v. Western union et al. New York City. Complaint., 1918; 1 (Reel 16)
    April 1918. 5 pp.
  - Commercial Telegraphers et al. v. Western union et al. New York City. Summary of Case., 1918; 2 (Reel 16)
    July 1918. 6 pp.
  - Summary Minutes of Executive Session, with a Report on the Controversy by Frank P. Walsh and William H. Taft., 1918; 3 (Reel 16)
    June 1, 1918. 7 pp.
  - William H. Taft to Newcomb Carlton., 1918; 4 (Reel 16)
    June 1918. 3 pp.
  - The Western Union and the War Labor Board: the Company's Position., 1918; 5 (Reel 16)
  - Exhibit: Memorandum of the Commercial Telegraphers of America., 1918; 6 (Reel 16)
  - Exhibit: the Association of Western Union Employees., 1918; 7 (Reel 16)
  - Exhibit: Reinstatements., 1918; 8 (Reel 16)
  - Exhibit: Discrimination., 1918; 9 (Reel 16)
  - Industrial Autocracy in the Telegraph Companies by S.J. Konenkamp., 1918; 10 (Reel 16)
    June 1918. 5 pp.
  - Appeal of the Commercial Telegraphers Union., 1919; 11 (Reel 16)
    October 1918 to January 18, 1919. 12 pp.
  - Memorandum for Mr. Lauck, including an Extract from the Minutes Bearing on the Western Union Case., 1919; 12 (Reel 16)
    March 1919. 21 pp.
  - Rulings., 1919; 13 (Reel 16)
    April 1919. 3 pp.
  - Correspondence from Union and Employees (Selections)., 1918-1919; 14 (Reel 16)
  - Correspondence with Newcomb Carleton., 1918; 15 (Reel 16)
  - Letters from Employees to President Woodrow Wilson (Selections)., 1918; 16 (Reel 16)
  - Correspondence with Postmaster General Burleson., 1918-1919; 17 (Reel 16)
  - Cranemen, et al. v. General Electric. Schenectady, NY.: Transcript of Hearing., 1918; 18 (Reel 16)
    May 18, 1918. 53 pp.
  - Briefs and Data of the Schenectady Metal Trades Council., 1918; 19 (Reel 16)
  - Rebuttal to Statement of General Electric by Schenectady Metal Trades Council., 1918; 20 (Reel 16)
  - Rebuttal to Oral and Written Statements of General Electric and to Exhibits B, C, D, and E by Schenectady Metal Trades Council., 1918; 21 (Reel 16)
    44 pp.
  - Statement of Central New York District of Electrical Workers of the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Supplementary to the Brief of the Schenectady Metal Trades Council., 1918; 22 (Reel 16)
  - Exhibits Submitted by General Electric., 1918; 23 (Reel 16)
  - Exhibit A: Proposition Made to the Schenectady Metal Trades Council., 1918; 24 (Reel 16)
  - Exhibit: Price Change and Cost of Living Statistics between 1914 and 1918., 1914-1918; 25 (Reel 16)
  - Exhibit D: Statement of Average Placework Earnings per Hour., 1918; 26 (Reel 16)
  - Exhibit E: Memoranda of Wages Paid by General Electric at Schenectady., 1912-1918; 27 (Reel 16)
  - Exhibit F: Statement of Earnings of Mechanics Outside of Schenectady., 1918; 28 (Reel 16)
  - Exhibit G: Comparison of Course of Average Hourly Earnings of Schenectady Factory Workers with Course of Retail Food Prices in the United States., 1914- 1918; 29 (Reel 16)
  - Correspondence (Selections)., 1918; 30 (Reel 16)
    38 pp.
  - Machinists et al. v. Bethlehem Steel. Bethlehem, PA: Transcript of Investigation., 1918; 31 (Reel 16)
    June 18, 1918. 243 pp.
  - Review of Testimony in the Bethlehem Steel Case., 1918; 32 (Reel 16)
    June 26, 1918. 29 pp.
  - Exhibit 1c: Sworn Deposition of Employees., 1918; 33 (Reel 16)
    May 1918. 20 pp.
  - Exhibit 1e: Memorandum by Harold Calendar, Special National War Labor Board Field Representative., 1918; 34 (Reel 16)
    June 18, 1918. 5 pp.
  - Exhibit 2a: Letter from Mr. E.G. Grace, Company President, regarding Wages., 1918; 35 (Reel 16)
    May 1918. 7 pp.
  - Exhibit 2b: Letter from Mr. E.G. Grace regarding Work Status of Members of Union Committee Appearing in Washington., 1918; 36 (Reel 16)
    May 1918. 2 pp.
  - Exhibit 2c: Statement of Mr. E.G. Grace Showing Earnings of Machinists., 1918; 37 (Reel 16)
    May 1918. 4 pp.
  - Exhibit 2d: Instructions Issued by Company relative to Piecework, Bonus, etc., 1917; 38 (Reel 16)
  - Exhibit 2e Number of Men Working at Hourly Rate, Contract, and Piece Rates, by Shops., 1918; 39 (Reel 16)
  - Exhibit 2i: Report of Turnover in Force., 1918; 40 (Reel 16)
    May 1918. 11 pp.
  - Exhibit 2j: Report of Relief and Beneficial Association for Year Ending May 31, 1918., 1917-1918; 41 (Reel 16)
  - Exhibit 2k: Company Pamphlet, "Timely Hints for the Safety and Welfare of Our Employees.", 1916; 42 (Reel 16)
    45 pp.
  - Exhibit 2l: Employment Forms, etc., 1918; 43 (Reel 16)
  - Representative of Employees in Plants of Bethlehem Steel., 44 (Reel 16)
  - Constitution and Bylaws of the Relief and Beneficial Association., 1916; 45 (Reel 16)
  - History and Importance of the Bethlehem Steel Case., 46 (Reel 16)
  - Report on Hearing Held May 20, 1918., 47 (Reel 16)
    June 1918.3 pp.
  - Statements of Employees., 1918; 48 (Reel 16)
    June 1918. 37 pp.
  - Memorandum on the Importance of Bethlehem Steel to the War Effort., 1918; 49 (Reel 16)
    June 8, 1918. 2 pp.
  - Memorandum to Frank P. Walsh., 1918; 50 (Reel 16)
    June 20, 1918. 6 pp.
  - Propositions of the Employees., 1918; 51 (Reel 16)
  - Report to the National War Labor Board by Herbert H. Rice., 1918; 52 (Reel 16)
    July 1918. 9 pp.
  - Conclusions Submitted by the Secretary and Chief Examiner., 1918; 53 (Reel 16)
    July 9, 1918. 7 pp.
  - Notes on the Shop Committee System for Bethlehem Steel by F.H. Bird., 1918; 54 (Reel 16)
    August 17, 1918 and September 5, 1918. 10 pp.
  - Shop Employment and Wage Statistics., 1918; 55 (Reel 16)
    May 1918. 13 pp.
  - Report on the Administration of the Clause affecting Women in the Award of Plants of the Bethlehem Steel Company, by B.H. Hienburg., 1918; 56 (Reel 16)
    August 31, 1918. 15 pp.
  - Extract from Minutes of the Executive Session., 1918; 57 (Reel 16)
    September 15, 1918. PM. 8 pp.
  - National War Labor Board, Bulletin 1, Statement to the Workers of Bethlehem Steel., 1918; 58 (Reel 16)
    October 9, 1918. 2 pp.
  - Memorandum on First Meeting of the Rules Committee of Employees., 1918; 59 (Reel 16)
    November 15, 1918. 2 pp.
  - Results of Shop Committee Elections., 1918; 60 (Reel 16)
    October-November, 1918. 6 pp.
  - Agnes Johnson to Elisabeth Chritman, Letter regarding Women Employees in Shop Committee Election., 1918; 61 (Reel 16)
    November 21, 1918. 1 p.
  - E.H. Grace to the National War Labor Board, Letter regarding Company Attitude toward Collective Bargaining., 1918; 62 (Reel 16)
    December 12, 1918. 4 pp.
  - National War Labor Board Correspondence on the Administration of the Award in the Bethlehem Case., 1918; 63 (Reel 16)
    November-December, 1918. 7 pp.
  - Statement of Situation in regard to Electrical Workers in Bethlehem Steel., 1918; 64 (Reel 16)
    December 2, 1918. 4 pp.
  - Complaint of Machinists regarding Company Actions., 1918; 65 (Reel 16)
    December 20, 1918. 1 p.
  - Correspondence of Richard B. Gregg, Examiner in Charge, regarding Rulings., 1918; 66 (Reel 16)
    November-December, 1918. 42 pp.
  - Rulings of the National War Labor Board., 1918-1919; 67 (Reel 16)
    November 1918-January 1919.15 pp.
  - Correspondence of Richard B. Gregg, Examiner in Charge., 1918; 68 (Reel 16)
    December 1918. 18 pp.
- Case Files (Selected Cases) continued (Reel 17)
  - Machinists et al. v. Bethlehem Steel. Bethlehem, PA. continued@ Correspondence of Richard B. Gregg, Examiner in Charge, continued, 1918; 1 (Reel 17)
    December 1918. 5 pp.
  - Shop Committee Elections Materials., 1918; 2 (Reel 17)
    22p.
  - Data relating to Shop Committee System, including the Administration of the Bethlehem Steel Award and Ways in Which the Company Is Derelict in the Award., 1918; 3 (Reel 17)
    October-December, 1918. 26 pp.
  - Transcript of Proceedings., 1919; 4 (Reel 17)
    January 18, 1919. AM. 5 pp.
  - Statement regarding Administration of the Bethlehem Award by E.B. Woods, Chief Administrator., 1919; 5 (Reel 17)
    January 1919. 6 pp.
  - Extent to Which the Company Has Compiled with the Provisions of Findings., 1919; 6 (Reel 17)
    January 1919. 5 pp.
  - Actions of the Board relative to the Application of Its Award., 7 (Reel 17)
  - Memorandum on Bethlehem Contracts and the Navy Department., 1919; 8 (Reel 17)
    January 1919. 1 p.
  - Correspondence of William H. Taft with Paul D. Cravath and Herbert H. Rice., 1919; 9 (Reel 17)
    January-February 1919.6 pp.
  - Correspondence of Thomas Barr, Committeeman of the Crucible Department and Richard B. Gregg, Examiner in Charge., 1918-1919; 10 (Reel 17)
    December 1918-January 1919. 15 pp.
  - Statement by Paul D. Cravath, Counsel for Bethlehem Steel., 1919; 11 (Reel 17)
    February 4, 1919. 4 pp.
  - Original Labor Proposals for an Adjustment of the Bethlehem Award., 12 (Reel 17)
  - Modified Labor Proposals for an Adjustment of the Bethlehem Award., 13 (Reel 17)
  - Results of Conference between Representatives of the Company and Its Employees., 14 (Reel 17)
  - Report on Shop Committee System at Bethlehem Steel, Lebanon Plant, by F.H. Bird., 1919; 15 (Reel 17)
    February 13, 1919.4 pp.
  - What Labor Did and Did Not Do at Bethlehem, by William H. Taft., 16 (Reel 17)
  - Dave Williams to W. Jett Lauck, Telegram on Disruptive Company Policies., 1919; 17 (Reel 17)
    March 3, 1919. 1 p.
  - Proposals for Plan of Collective Bargaining Submitted by Committeemen., 1919; 18 (Reel 17)
  - Company's Observations on Proposals for Plan of Collective Bargaining Submitted by Committeemen., 1919; 19 (Reel 17)
    February 1919. 5 pp.
  - Further Comments by Company on Plan of Collective Bargaining., 1919; 20 (Reel 17)
    March 3, 1919. 4 pp.
  - Plan of Collective Bargaining., 1919; 21 (Reel 17)
    April 1919. 6 pp.
  - Suggestions Looking toward an Adjustment of the Bethlehem Award., 22 (Reel 17)
  - Decision of the National War Labor Board., 1919; 23 (Reel 17)
    April 11, 1919. 8 pp.
  - Summary and Transcript of Testimony on Machinists' and Electricians' Controversies., 24 (Reel 17)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Divisions 268 and 26 v. Cleveland Railway and Detroit United Railway. Cleveland, OH and Detroit, MI.: Summary of Hearing in Controversy., 1918; 25 (Reel 17)
    May 28, 1918.8 pp.
  - History of Dispute in Docket 31., 1918; 26 (Reel 17)
  - Statement of the Cleveland Railway Company., 1918; 27 (Reel 17)
    June 1918. 66 pp.
  - Brief of Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 268 and 26., 1918; 28 (Reel 17)
    June 1918. 112 pp.
  - Original Complaint in Docket 491: Employees v. Cleveland Street Railway. Cleveland, OH., 1918; 29 (Reel 17)
    September-December 1918. 16 pp.
  - Report of City Street Railroad Commissioner (Cleveland) for the Year 1917 and the First Six Months of 1918., 1917-1918; 30 (Reel 17)
  - Correspondence regarding the Dismissal of Women Railway Employees in Cleveland., 1918-1919; 31 (Reel 17)
    September 1918-March 1919. 32 pp.
  - Summary of the Dispute in Docket 32: Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 26 v. Detroit United Railways., 1918; 32 (Reel 17)
    June 1918. 6 pp.
  - Statement of the Detroit United Railway., 1918; 33 (Reel 17)
    May 27, 1918. 87 pp.
  - Exhibits of Wages of the Detroit United Railway., 1906-1918; 34 (Reel 17)
  - Report on the Earnings, Operating Expenses, Service, and Rate of Fare of the Detroit United Railway, by Barclay, Parsons, and Klapp., 1918; 35 (Reel 17)
    April 1918. 106 pp.
  - Correspondence regarding the Administration of the Award in Docket 32., 1918; 36 (Reel 17)
    April-August 1918. 65 pp.
  - Machinists, Local 30, 782, and 826 v. Employers. Bridgeport, CT: Correspondence with Secretary of War Newton Baker, 1917-1918; 37 (Reel 17)
    December 1917-February 1918. 3 pp.
  - Complaint of International Association of Machinists., 1918; 38 (Reel 17)
    June 1918. 14 pp.
  - Hearing before the Mediation Branch of the Industrial Service Section of the US Army Ordnance Department regarding Machinists' and Toolmakers' Requests for Increase in Wages in Certain Bridgeport Factories., 1918; 39 (Reel 17)
    May 23, 1918. 21 pp.
  - Memoranda from Ordnance Department., 1918; 40 (Reel 17)
    May 4 and July 7, 1918. 2 pp.
  - Referral of Case to the National War Labor Board by Secretary of War Newton Baker., 1918; 41 (Reel 17)
    June 24, 1918. 2 pp.
  - Summary of Case., 1918; 42 (Reel 17)
    July 31, 1918. 5 pp.
  - Brief of Remington Arms., 1918; 43 (Reel 17)
    July 19, 1918. 28 pp.
  - Brief of Manufacturers Other Than Remington Arms., 44 (Reel 17)
    32 pp.
  - Proposed Finding Submitted by the Employers., 45 (Reel 17)
  - Statement of Machinists, Local 30, 782 and 826 concerning Wages and Working Conditions., 1918; 46 (Reel 17)
    July 1, 1918. 17 pp.
  - Exhibits to Machinists' Statement., 1918; 47 (Reel 17)
    August 1918. 19 pp.
  - Statement of Mr. Wallace Speaking for Remington Arms before the National War Labor Board., 48 (Reel 17)
  - Statement of Louis G. Kibbe, Vice President and General Manager of Stamford Rolling Mills., 49 (Reel 17)
  - The Basic Eight Hour Day: Argument on Behalf of Employer Members of the National War Labor Board., 50 (Reel 17)
  - Statement of Louis G. Kibbe, Vice President and General Manager of Stamford Rolling Mills., 51 (Reel 17)
  - The Basic Eight Hour Day: Argument on Behalf of Employer Members of the National War Labor Board., 1918; 52 (Reel 17)
    July 16, 1918. 19 pp.
  - Report and Recommendations, William H. Johnston., 53 (Reel 17)
  - Statement of C.E. Michael, Member., 1918; 54 (Reel 17)
    August 16, 1918. 8 pp.
  - Proclamation of the President of the United States Creating the National War Labor Board: Its Functions and Powers, Principles Governing Industry, and Method of Presenting Complaints and Procedures., 1918; 55 (Reel 17)
    April 8, 1918. 7 pp.
  - Points to be Considered., 56 (Reel 17)
  - The Fundamental Issue at Bridgeport and Suggestions regarding the Award., 1918; 57 (Reel 17)
    August 9, 1918. 10 pp.
  - Recommendations for the Award by Isaac Russell, Field Representative., 1918; 58 (Reel 17)
    August 4, 1918. 5 pp.
  - The Unsolved Issue at Bridgeport by Isaac Russell., 1918; 59 (Reel 17)
    July 27, 1918. 59 pp.
  - Addendum to Dockets 31 and 32: Street and Electric Railway Employees, Divisions 268 and 26 v. Cleveland Railway and Detroit United Railway. Cleveland, OH, and Detroit, MI. Addendum: Brief of Detroit United Railway., 1918; 60 (Reel 17)
    June 1918. 22 pp.
  - Brief of Street and Electric Railway Employees, Divisions 26 and 268., 1918; 61 (Reel 17)
    June 1918. 59 pp.
- Case Files (Selected Cases) continued (Reel 18)
  - Machinists, Locals 30, 782, and 826 v. Employers. Bridgeport, CT: Correspondence from Isaac Russell, Field Representative., 1918; 1 (Reel 18)
    August 1918. 8 pp.
  - Wage Investigation: Report of Statistical Committee of the Manufacturers Association of Bridgeport on Wage and Cost of Living Conditions., 1918; 2 (Reel 18)
    July 15, 1918. 25 pp.
  - Methods Followed in Eleventh Hour Survey to Collect Supplementary Wage Data for Women Workers in Bridgeport by Caroline E. Wilson., 3 (Reel 18)
  - Memorandum on Bridgeport Wage Data., 4 (Reel 18)
  - Findings of Arbitrators., 5 (Reel 18)
  - The Bridgeport Award., 6 (Reel 18)
  - The Bridgeport Award: Memorandum on Classification., 7 (Reel 18)
  - Comparison of Award in Bridgeport Case, Submitted by Mr. Walsh and Mr. Osborne., 8 (Reel 18)
  - Transcript of Executive Session of the National War Labor Board., 1918; 9 (Reel 18)
    August 16, 1918. PM. 256 pp.
  - Exhibits., 1918; 10 (Reel 18)
  - Exhibit: Statement of the National Industrial Conference Board respecting the National Labor Situation., 1917; 11 (Reel 18)
  - Exhibit: War Department Instructions to Biddgers on Fixed Price and Cost Plus Profit Contracts., 1917; 12 (Reel 18)
  - Exhibits Presented by the Government, 1917-1918; 13 (Reel 18)
    55 pp.
  - President Woodrow Wilson to the Bridgeport Machinists, 1918; 14 (Reel 18)
    September 13, 1918. Letter and Attachments. 6 pp.
  - Secretary of War Newton Baker to W. Jett Lauck., 1918; 15 (Reel 18)
    September 3, 1918. 3 pp.
  - Rulings of the National War Labor Board., 1918; 16 (Reel 18)
    September 23, 1918.
  - Statement of Willard H. Sink., 1918; 17 (Reel 18)
    August 20, 1918. 5 pp.
  - Complaint against Remington Arms., 1918; 18 (Reel 18)
    October 10, 1918. 5 pp.
  - History and Interpretation of the Award., 1918; 19 (Reel 18)
    August-November 1918. 8 pp.
  - History and Interpretation of the Award., 1918; 20 (Reel 18)
    August-December 1918. 7 pp.
  - Minutes of Meeting of the Local Board of Mediation and Conciliation., 1918; 21 (Reel 18)
    November 4, 1918. 13 pp.
  - Minutes of Meeting of the Local Board of Mediation and Conciliation., 1918; 22 (Reel 18)
    November 8, 1918. 13 pp.
  - Minutes of Meeting of the Local Board of Mediation and Conciliation., 1918; 23 (Reel 18)
    November 21, 1918. 42 pp.
  - Organization and Bylaws for Collective Bargaining Committees, Instituted by the National War Labor Board., 1918; 24 (Reel 18)
    November 26, 1918. 13 pp.
  - Correspondence. (Selections)., 1918; 25 (Reel 18)
    June-December 1918. 91 pp.
  - Briefs Appealing Examiner's Ruling 14 on Behalf of Remington Arms., 1919; 26 (Reel 18)
    March 6, 1919. 10 pp.
  - Briefs Appealing Examiner's Ruling 17 on Behalf of Remington Arms., 27 (Reel 18)
  - Briefs Appealing Examiner's Ruling 14 on Behalf of Manufacturers Other Than Remington Arms., 1919; 28 (Reel 18)
    March 6, 1919. 5p.
  - Briefs Appealing Examiner's Ruling 17 on Behalf of Manufactures Other than Remington Arms., 1919; 29 (Reel 18)
    March 13, 1919. 6 pp.
  - Briefs Appealing Examiner's Ruling 14 on Behalf of Employees. Reply Brief., 1919; 30 (Reel 18)
    March 15, 1919. 5 pp.
  - Memorandum on Examiner's Rulings by District 55 of International Association of Machinists., 1919; 31 (Reel 18)
    March 14, 1919. 3 pp.
  - Briefs Appealing Examiner's Ruling 17 on Behalf of Guards and Watchmen at Remington Arms., 32 (Reel 18)
  - Reply Brief of Guards and Watchmen to Remington Arms Brief on Ruling 17 and to That of Manufacturers Other Than Remington Arms., 33 (Reel 18)
  - Reply Brief of Guards and Watchmen to Manufacturers' Brief on Ruling 17., 34 (Reel 18)
  - Brief Appealing Examiner's Ruling 14 on Behalf of Viola Leonik., 1918; 35 (Reel 18)
    December 6, 1918. 4 pp.
  - Briefs Appealing Examiner's Ruling 14 on Behalf of George Polisin et al., 1918; 36 (Reel 18)
    December 6, 1918. 3 pp.
  - Briefs Appealing Examiner's Ruling 17 on Behalf of Guards and Watchmen at American and British manufacturing., 1919; 37 (Reel 18)
    March 22, 1919. 6 pp.
  - Employees Brief Covering the Appeal from Examiner's Ruling 17 on Behalf of Guards at Remington Arms., 1919; 38 (Reel 18)
    March 10, 1919. 3 pp.
  - Employees Brief Covering the Appeal from Examiner's Ruling 17 on Behalf of Guards at American Can., 1919; 39 (Reel 18)
  - Minutes of Meeting of the Local Board of Mediation and Conciliation., 1919; 40 (Reel 18)
    March 31, 1919. 31 pp.
  - Rulings of the National War Labor Board., 1918-1919; 41 (Reel 18)
    September 23, 1918 and February 19, 1919. 7 pp.
  - Correspondence., 1919; 42 (Reel 18)
    January-April 1919. 85 pp.
  - Remington Arms Corrected Version of Transcript of Hearing, Testimony of Mr. Wallace for the Company., 1918; 43 (Reel 18)
    July 2, 1918. 32 pp.
  - List of Cases Referred to the National War Labor Board by the War Department and the Navy Department., 1919; 44 (Reel 18)
    June 9, 1919. 7 pp.
  - Lynn Central Labor Union et al. v. General Electric. Lynn, MA: Original Complaint., 1918; 45 (Reel 18)
    August 1918. 5 pp.
  - Report of the US Commissioner of Conciliation with Exhibits., 1918; 46 (Reel 18)
    September 21, 1918. 23 pp.
  - Brief Submitted by Lynn Works, General Electric Company., 1918; 47 (Reel 18)
    August 1918. 100 pp.
- Case Files (Selected Cases) continued; Interstaff Communications (Selections) (Reel 19)
  - Lynn Central Labor Union et al. v. General Electric. Lynn, MA cont.: Exhibits Submitted by the Lynn Works, General Electric Company., 1918; 1 (Reel 19)
    August 1918. 15 pp.
  - Rebuttal Brief Submitted by Employees of Lynn Plant of General Electric Company., 1918; 2 (Reel 19)
    90 pp.
  - Supplemental Brief with Exhibits of the Employees., 1918; 3 (Reel 19)
    August 15, 1918. 17 pp.
  - Exhibits to Employees Brief., 1918; 4 (Reel 19)
  - Schedules B-N: Briefs Submitted on Behalf of Various Trades., 1918; 5 (Reel 19)
    August 1918. 51 pp.
  - Statement of the Management of the Lynn Works of General Electric., 1918; 6 (Reel 19)
    September 24, 1918. 8 pp.
  - Representation of Employees, Pamphlet Issued by General Electric., 1918; 7 (Reel 19)
    September 1918. 21 pp.
  - General Summary of the Case by Examiner Edwin Newdick., 1918; 8 (Reel 19)
    September 26, 1918. 22 pp.
  - Examiner's Memorandum on Lynn General Electric Case., 1918; 9 (Reel 19)
    September 28, 1918. 2 pp.
  - Preliminary Draft of Award by Examiner., 1918; 10 (Reel 19)
    October 2, 1918. 4 pp.
  - Recommendations for Award regarding Discharged Men by Examiner., 11 (Reel 19)
  - Brief of the Reinstatement of White and Peterson Submitted on Behalf of the Employees., 12 (Reel 19)
  - Memorandum on the Company's Committee Plan., 1918; 13 (Reel 19)
    October 1918. 3 pp.
  - Recommended Award Affecting Women in the Lynn Plant., 1918; 14 (Reel 19)
    November 1918. 2 pp.
  - Cost of Living Budget: Digest of Information relative to This Subject Collected from 98 Women Employees by Elanor C. Karsten., 15 (Reel 19)
  - General Statement regarding Time and System of Payment for Women Employees., 16 (Reel 19)
  - Women Labor in the Plant of General Electric Epitomized by Chief Woman Examiner., 1918; 17 (Reel 19)
    November 1918. 3 pp.
  - Work Done by Women in General Electric Plant at Lynn by Bertha M. Nienburg., 18 (Reel 19)